{
    "subject": "resource/Eve_von_Bibra",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1966-06-27",
    "human_readable": "Eve von Bibra was born on June 27th, 1966.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8810693025588989,
            "question": "When was Eve von Bibra born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8696041703224182,
            "question": "Is June the month Eve von Bibra was born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7705583572387695,
            "question": "What is Eve von Bibra's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7237754464149475,
            "question": "In what month was Eve von Bibra born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7086043357849121,
            "question": "Is Eve von Bibra older or younger than someone born on January 1st, 1967?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6986622214317322,
            "question": "What day of the week was Eve von Bibra born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44658362865448,
            "question": "Calculate Eve von Bibra's age."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4389263093471527,
            "question": "If today is July 1st, 2023, how many days have passed since Eve von Bibra was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3632011413574219,
            "question": "What year is 20 years after Eve von Bibra's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3609475791454315,
            "question": "How old will Eve von Bibra be in 5 years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eve von Bibra was born on June 27th, 1966.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1112_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year is 20 years after Eve von Bibra's birth year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1112_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is July 1st, 2023, how many days have passed since Eve von Bibra was born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1112_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Calculate Eve von Bibra's age.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1112_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1112_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the information in the documents (specifically, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1112/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1112/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt) confirms that Eve von Bibra was indeed born on June 27th, 1966."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provided include the date of birth for Eve Sarah von Bibra as 27 June 1966, which supports the statement that she was born on June 27th, 1966."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}